<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pizza Recipes</string>

    <string name="first_pizza_name">Next level Margherita pizza</string>
    <string name="first_pizza_description">Forget takeaways – you can\'t beat a homemade Margherita
        pizza topped with fresh tomato sauce and melted cheese. Here\'s how to master this everyday
        classic…</string>
    <string name="first_pizza_recipe">STEP 1\n
First, make the dough. Tip the flour into a bowl and add 300ml tepid water. Mix together and set aside at room temperature for 1 hr. Dissolve the yeast in 2 tbsp water and mix this and 15g of salt through the dough. Cover with cling film and leave somewhere warm to double in size for a few hours. For a sourer flavour, leave in the fridge for at least 8 hrs and up to 24 hrs – the longer you leave it the sourer it will be.
\n\n
STEP 2\n
When the dough is ready, tip it onto a lightly floured surface and divide into four. Roll into balls and leave to rest, covered with a tea towel or cling film for another hour.
\n\n
STEP 3\n
Now make the tomato sauce. Drain some of the juice from the can and tip the rest into a bowl with the olive oil, oregano and a generous pinch of salt, then either scrunch everything together with your fingers for a chunky sauce or blitz with a stick blender if you want it smooth. Tie the basil stalks together, bruise with the back of a knife and place in the sauce. Leave the sauce at room temperature until needed.
\n\n
STEP 4\n
To make the pizza, heat a grill to its highest setting and get a heavy frying pan. On a floured surface push and stretch one of the balls of dough out into a circle roughly the same size as the frying pan. Slip the round onto a floured baking sheet and top with a quarter of the sauce, a scattering of cheese, a few basil leaves and a quarter of the mozzarella.
\n\n
STEP 5\n
Get the pan very hot and carefully slide the pizza onto it. Cook for 2 mins, then put the pan under the grill for another 2 mins until the sides are puffed up and the cheese has melted. Lift onto a board, drizzle with a little olive oil if you like, then cut into wedges and serve while you make the next one.</string>

    <string name="second_pizza_name">Pizza Margherita in 4 easy steps</string>
    <string name="second_pizza_description">Even a novice cook can master the art of perfect pizza
        with our step-by-step guide. This homemade pizza recipe features a simple pizza dough and
        toppings.</string>
    <string name="second_pizza_recipe">STEP 1\n
Make the base: Put the flour into a large bowl, then stir in the yeast and salt. Make a well, pour in 200ml warm water and the olive oil and bring together with a wooden spoon until you have a soft, fairly wet dough. Turn onto a lightly floured surface and knead for 5 mins until smooth. Cover with a tea towel and set aside. You can leave the dough to rise if you like, but it’s not essential for a thin crust.
\n\n
STEP 2\n
Make the sauce: Mix the passata, basil and crushed garlic together, then season to taste. Leave to stand at room temperature while you get on with shaping the base.
\n\n
STEP 3\n
Roll out the dough: if you’ve let the dough rise, give it a quick knead, then split into two balls. On a floured surface, roll out the dough into large rounds, about 25cm across, using a rolling pin. The dough needs to be very thin as it will rise in the oven. Lift the rounds onto two floured baking sheets.
\n\n
STEP 4\n
Top and bake: heat the oven to 240C/220C fan/gas 8. Put another baking sheet or an upturned baking tray in the oven on the top shelf. Smooth sauce over bases with the back of a spoon. Scatter with cheese and tomatoes, drizzle with olive oil and season. Put one pizza, still on its baking sheet, on top of the preheated sheet or tray. Bake for 8-10 mins until crisp. Serve with a little more olive oil, and basil leaves if using. Repeat step for remaining pizza.</string>

    <string name="third_pizza_name">Caramelized onion &amp; goats cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="third_pizza_description">Make a veggie pizza that\'s healthy and low-fat instead
        of ordering a takeaway. This easy recipe uses goat\'s cheese for tang while the onions give
        it sweetness</string>
    <string name="third_pizza_recipe">STEP 1\n
Heat oven to 220C/200C fan/gas 7. Tip the flour into a mixer with a dough hook, or a bowl. Add the yeast, salt, oil and just under 100ml warm water then mix to a soft dough. Knead in the food mixer for about 5 mins, but if making this by hand, tip onto a work surface and knead for about 10 mins. The dough is sticky, but try not to add too much extra flour. Leave in the bowl and cover with a tea towel while you make the topping. There is no need to let the dough prove for a specific time – just let it sit while you get on with the next step.
\n\n
STEP 2\n
Tip the onions into a non-stick wok and add the oil, 4 tbsp water and balsamic vinegar. Cover with a saucepan lid that sits inside the pan to help the onions soften, then cook for 15 mins, stirring about 3 times and replacing the lid quickly so as not to lose too much moisture. After the time is up, the onions should be golden and all the liquid gone. Tip onto a plate. Add the spinach and garlic to the pan and stir-fry until the spinach has wilted.
\n\n
STEP 3\n
Take the dough from the bowl and cut in half with an oiled knife, then press each piece into a 25-15 cm oval on a large greased baking sheet with oiled hands. Don’t knead the dough first otherwise it will be too elastic and it will keep shrinking back.
\n\n
STEP 4\n
Spread with the spinach followed by the onions, then dot with the cheese and scatter with the olives, thyme and sunflower seeds. Bake for 15 mins until golden and the base is cooked through.</string>

    <string name="fourth_pizza_name">Christmas tree pizza</string>
    <string name="fourth_pizza_description">Bring festive fun to dinnertime with our tree-shaped
        pizza made with shop-bought pastry. Choose your own toppings, such as pancetta, chopped
        chipolatas and pesto</string>
    <string name="fourth_pizza_recipe">STEP 1\n
Heat the oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Unroll the pastry and use a small, sharp knife to cut out a large Christmas tree shape, reserving any offcuts. Carefully lift the pastry tree onto a large baking sheet lined with baking parchment.
\n\n
STEP 2\n
Spread over the tomato sauce, pushing it right to the edges. Sprinkle over the cheese and any toppings. Spread the pesto over the pastry offcuts and cut most of these into 1cm-wide strips using a pizza cutter. Twist and arrange over the tree to make ‘tinsel’. Stamp out stars or other shapes from any remaining offcuts, then use to decorate the tree or bake alongside it.
\n\n
STEP 3\n
Bake for 20-25 mins (removing any shapes baked alongside after 15 mins) until the pastry is puffed up and golden and the cheese has melted. Serve straightaway.</string>

    <string name="fifth_pizza_name">Homemade turkish lahmacun</string>
    <string name="fifth_pizza_description">Sometimes called \'Turkish pizza\', this crispy flatbread
        topped with spiced mincemeat is a popular street food across the Middle East</string>
    <string name="fifth_pizza_recipe">STEP 1\n
Sift the flour into a large bowl, make a well in the middle and sprinkle in the yeast. Pour 125ml water over the yeast, then flick flour over the liquid to create a layer. Cover and leave to rise in a warm place for 15 mins until cracks appear on the surface of that layer.
\n\n
STEP 2\n
Use your hands to mix in 250ml more water along with 1 tsp salt and knead the dough for about 10 mins until elastic and no longer sticky. Add a little more flour if you need to. Cover and leave to rise again in a warm place for 30 mins until doubled in size.
\n\n
STEP 3\n
Heat the oven to as high as it will go (about 240C/220C fan/gas 9) and sprinkle one or two baking trays thinly with cornmeal.
\n\n
STEP 4\n
Pour boiling water from the kettle over the tomatoes, leave to stand briefly, then drain and slip off the skins. Cut the tomatoes in half, cut out the stalks, scoop out the seeds and discard, then chop the flesh.
\n\n
STEP 5\n
Halve the chillies lengthways, cut out the stalks, seeds and white inner membrane, then rinse. Cut lengthwise into fine strips, then crosswise into fine dice.
\n\n
STEP 6\n
Put the tomatoes, chillies, spring onions, finely chopped parsley, beef mince, spices, 1 tsp salt and ½ tsp freshly ground black pepper into a bowl and mix well.
\n\n
STEP 7\n
Take the dough and knead it briefly, then divide into four pieces and shape each into a ball. Roll each ball into a thin circle, place on the prepared baking trays. Spread with a thin layer of the meat mixture.
\n\n
STEP 8\n
Bake each flatbread for 10-15 mins until the edges begin to darken. After removing from the oven, sprinkle the lahmacun with the roughly chopped parsley and sliced onion, then squeeze over a few drops of lemon juice. Serve straightaway.</string>

</resources>